https://italianculinary.it/privacy/

Privacy & Cookies
Italian Culinary Institute Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from http://www.italianculinary.it and http://www.italianculinaryinstitute.com (the “Sites”).PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Sites, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. We may use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Sites–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.You can opt out of targeted advertising by:COMMON LINKS INCLUDE:FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=adsGOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymousBING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads]]Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Sites’ data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@italianculinary.it or by mail using the details provided below:Loc Caminia, Staletti, 78, 88069, Italy
Privacy Regarding Websites*Following Italian Law 675/96 on «Protection of individuals and other subjects with regard to the processing of personal data», the Italian Culinary Institute guarantees that personal data processing will be held lawfully and fairly, protecting your privacy and your rights.As per art.10 of said Law, we hereafter provide you with the information on ways and goals of the data processing that we will do on the data we collected: We will process your personal data for keeping an electronic or traditional mailing list.Any data you provide will not be on-line, will not visible to anyone, and no one besides you will be informed of your belonging to any mailing list or on-line service. The goal of data processing is only to update you on our Company and our activities and products. You always have the possibility to unsubscribe from our services, and being canceled from mailing lists and other electronic data processing devices, by simply writing an e-mail to e-mail@intercomm.it.Your personal data will always remain secret, and will not be handed to any other Company or person outside the Italian Culinary Institute without asking your consent. The data processing controller is the Italian Culinary Institute .You can contact the controller any time you feel your rights are being violated, as per art. 13 of Law 675/96.For book or other item purchases through websites in partnership with “Amazon.com”, websites are obligated to the following:You acknowledge that, by participating in the Associates Program and placing any of the above links within your site, Amazon.com may receive information from or about visitors to your site or communications between your site and those visitors. Your participation in the Amazon.com program constitutes your specific and unconditional consent to and authorization for Amazon.com’s access to, receipt, storage, use, and disclosure of any and all such information, consistent with the policies and procedures set forth in Amazon.com’s Privacy Notice.*”Website” implies all websites owned and/or operated by InterComm GROUP, Italian Culinary Institute and subsidiaries including but not limited to:http://www.italianculinary.ithttp://www.italianculinaryinstitute.com
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thanks
